http://vegalleries.com/policies

Skip to main content
IN LIGHT OF THE CURRENT HEALTH PANDEMIC AND TO HELP PREVENT THE SPREAD OF COVID-19 (coronavirus). VAN EATON GALLERIES WILL CURRENTLY BE CLOSED TO THE PUBLIC.We are still fulfilling online and phone orders through shipping and scheduled curbside pickup. CLICK HERE FOR MORE INFORMATION.
x
Policies
Terms of Use
Thank you for visiting Van Eaton Galleries at www.vegalleries.com.
Our goal is to provide a comprehensive experience for the animation collector and fan alike. Van Eaton Galleries allows the use of our website in accordance with the following conditions.
By using www.vegalleries.com, you agree to these conditions. Please take the time to thoroughly read them.
Our website provides a variety of imagery, information, and services, and there is the possibility that additional terms may apply for your specific use.
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to Van Eaton Galleries and this policy represents our commitment to care for your personal information. This privacy policy applies to the data Van Eaton Galleries collects on its websites and through any services associated with those sites. This policy does not cover data that you independently disclose to other users of the websites or services. Van Eaton Galleries complies with the the General Data Protection Regulation.
Additional information about information that we collect, the purpose of collection, and your rights are provided in detail within this Policy.
The Information We Collect From You:
·All information collected by Van Eaton Galleries has been collected either by request in person, or while you are using our websites or services.
We do not purchase mailing lists.
·When you register to use our website and services, Van Eaton Galleries collects minimal information to better serve you as a collector.
That information includes your username, email address, and first and last name.
·When you register to make a purchase through our website, other information is retained for shipping purposes and billing purposes.
This information includes your telephone number, mailing address, and billing address.
·You may also volunteer to provide us with information regarding your personal interests in collecting animation and related collectibles, so that we can alert you to artwork that arrives.
·We use cookies and other tracking technology to keep track of your online interactions with our site. These technologies may also be used to collect non-personally identifiable information to assist us in analyzing user interaction with our websites and services.
·We retain your personal information only as long as needed to provide you with services and assistance.
·The personal information that we collect is used to provide you with the specific services being requested, offer personalized services based upon your collecting preferences, and send you emails or physical mailers to keep you aware of upcoming events and art availability.
·VAN EATON GALLERIES NEVER SELLS OUR MAILING LIST TO OTHER COMPANIES OR INDIVIDUALS. If your information is shared with any other company, it is with the intention of sharing information with you about events or services being offered by a company working in conjunction with Van Eaton Galleries.
·If you are making a purchase through our website, no credit card or payment information is stored in our records.
All payment information is handled directly by our credit card processors.
International Shipping
Van Eaton Galleries is happy to assist collectors from all over the world. We currently use DHL to ship packages internationally to ensure fast and reliable service. The shipping fee that is quoted at the time of purchase does not include any additional fees. International orders may be subject to customs, importation, and tax fees based upon the recipient's location. These fees are the responsibility of the recipient and are not included in the quoted shipping fees on the recipient's order. Any packages that are returned as unclaimed will require additional postage fees. Any orders that are cancelled after a package has been shipped and returned will be eligible for store credit for the purchase price, not including shipping fees.
